>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 七年前，马克给了我开始教书的开始。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Seven years ago,
Mark gave me my start in teaching.
他跟我说，看到我给会议演讲，但是
He reached out to me,
had seen me giving conference talks, but
我从来没有在这个行业里教过任何东西
I had never taught anything
in this industry, whatsoever.
他说，嘿，我想你应该给它一次机会。
And he reached out and said, hey,
I think you should give it a shot.
他花了几周时间来找我
And he took a couple of weeks to coax me,
主要是因为我要去滑雪了，冷冰冰的明尼苏达
mostly because I was having to
come up to snowy, cold Minnesota.
但他花了几个星期的时间让我和我来到这里，给了我的第一次研讨会。
But he took a couple weeks to coax me and
I came up here and gave my first workshop.
从那天到那个时候，我心里想，这就是我想做的事，
And midway through that day, it clicked in
my mind that this is what I wanted to do,
这就是我在这儿教的东西
and this is what I'm here for,
is to teach.
所以我现在是全职老师，完全感谢马克。
So I'm a teacher now full-time,
thanks completely to Mark.
所以我一直很感激我总是觉得我要回家了
So I always appreciate that and
I always feel like I'm coming back home,
如果你愿意的话当我回到Fron趋向大师赛的时候
if you will,
when I come back to Frontend Masters.
所以我们要谈的是 JavaScript 和
So this course, we're gonna be
talking about JavaScript and
我们将会比你更深入的谈论这个问题
we're gonna be talking about it much more
deeply than you're used to likely going.
大多数人可能知道我有一个公平的
Most people may know that I have a fairly
" GETIFY " 名称下的强大在线存在。
strong online presence
under the name GETIFY.
所以如果你读了我的推特特别是最近
So if you've read my Twitter streams,
especially lately,
我在准备课程的时候经常谈这些东西
I've been talking a lot about all this
stuff while preparing the course.
但你可以在我的 Twitter上看到我的想法 GitHub
But you can find all of my
thoughts on my Twitter, on GitHub,
那是我的邮箱地址
that's my email address.
因此，我们可以自由地伸出或去寻找更多的信息。
So feel free to reach out or
look for more of that information.
我写了很多书，包括  系列。
I've written a number of books including
the You Don't Know JS book series.
这门课上的很多材料直接用前三本的
A lot of material from this course tracks
directly with the first three major books
系列的数据。
of the series.
" 范围和关闭 " 一书， " 此 " 和 " 对象原型 " 一书，以及
The Scope and Closures book,
the This &amp; Object Prototypes book, and
一书。
the Types &amp; Grammar book.
因此，这些都是在这一过程中获得更多信息的最佳场所。
So those are the best places to go after
this course to get more information.
可以免费阅读，也可以购买。
You can read those for free or
you can purchase them.
我一直很感谢你的购买
I always appreciate
purchases if you like those.
所以我想和你谈谈为什么我们要跳进 JavaScript
So I wanna talk to you a little bit about
why we're gonna jump into JavaScript so
更深刻的
much more deeply.
而不是对各种框架和首字母缩略词进行广泛调查，
Rather than a broad survey of every kind
of framework and acronym that's possible,
为什么我们要深入到 JavaScript 中，为什么今天会有这个问题呢 ?
why are we diving deep into JavaScript,
and why does that even matter today?
因为现在看来连 JavaScript 都没人写了。
Because it seems the trend is nobody
even writes JavaScript anymore.
他们写点别的无论是 TypeScript 还是
They write something else,
whether it's TypeScript or
一种完全不同的语言，比如 Go 或 Closure。
an entirely different language like Go or
Closure.
但似乎没有人真正写出自己的JavaScript 。
But nobody seems to really
write their JavaScript.
我是说连他们写的 JavaScript 都没有了
I mean, nobody even ships
JavaScript that they wrote anymore.
他们提供了 14 层 Babble 变换的代码。
They ship the code that 14 layers of
Babble transformations have done.
所以为什么我们要学会和理解
So why does it even matter why
we learn and understand and
我们为什么要学习和理解 JavaScript?
why should we learn and
understand JavaScript?
所以我想简单的说，这就是我们将要报道的事情的概观。
So I wanna, just a quick brief, this is an
overview of what we're gonna be covering.
这很明显是很简单的代码
This is obviously very simple code, but
这其实是我经历过的
this is actually something
that I experienced or
我最近才了解到这个过程的准备和建设。
I learned just recently, in the
preparation and buildup to this course.
所以你们中的大多数可能都知道 ++ 运营商的情况。
So most of you probably
know about the ++ operator.
当它出现在后缀位置上就像在第 3 行
And that when it shows up in the postfix
position, like it is here on line 3,
当它出现在那个后置位置时它是一个增量
when it shows up in that postfixed
position it's an after increment.
所以它给你这个值，然后是递增的，这就是为什么 x++ 仍然返回
So it gives you the value and then it
increments, which is why x++ still returns
我们 40岁但那 X 已经更新到 41了
us 40, but then x has been updated to 41.
然后在第 6 行预先增量更新
And then on line 6 we have
the pre-increment which does the updating
首先，然后返回值，这就是为什么在该行上同时获得两个 42s。
first and then returns the value,
which is why on that line we get both 42s.
现在我的头和大部分的开发者都在脑中
Now I've had in my head and I think most
developers have had in their head a mental
+ + 运算符正在执行的操作的模型。
model for what the ++ operator is doing.
是啊那是之前和之后的细微差别
Yes, there's the before and
after kind of nuance, but
在我脑海中，基本上，这个 ++ 运算符基本上是 x+1。
I've had in my mind that essentially,
this ++ operator is basically x+1.
我认为大多数人都认为情况就是这样。
And I think most people probably
think that that is the case.
所以我特别调查了这个
And so
I was digging into this in particular, and
后来你就会知道为什么我这么想
you'll find out later in
the course why I was thinking so
对这种微妙的事情有很深的了解
deeply about something as
sort of nuanced as this.
但我想知道你是否有过某种价值
But I was trying to think about if
you have ++ on some value and it's in
position 位置，这是否表示该值完全未受影响?
the postfix position, does that mean that
the value comes back completely untouched?
我以为是这个案子把这个价值完全没有触及的
I assumed that that was the case, that it
returned the value completely untouched
然后把它更新的任何增量都做了
and then it made whatever
increments it updated.
那么问题就变成，当你在那个后缀中使用 ++ 的时候会发生什么
So the question then becomes, well, what
happens when you use ++ in that postfix
位置，但在某些值上使用该位置，但该值不是数字吗 ?
position, but you use it on some
value that's not already a number?
我们会在这门课上讲类型和
And we're gonna be talking in just a
little bit in this course about types and
强迫。
coercion.
我要深入讨论这个话题
And I'm gonna get real
deep into this topic.
但问题变成了
But the question becomes,
当一个数字和一个数字的字符串表示
what happens when there's a string
representation of a number and
那么你会做一些基本的事情比如增加它吗
then you do something fundamentally
mathematic like incrementing it?
在我思想过程中，因为 x ++ l=x +1，
In my mind thought process, again,
because thinking of x++ as x equals x+1,
我在想，那么它会把这个串五回来，
I was thinking, well,
it will return this string 5, and
然后它会将字符串 5 强制为 5 并更新为 6。
then it'll coerce that string 5 to
the number 5 and update it to 6.
那是我的精神模型
That was the mental model I had.
事实证明，尽管这似乎是合理的，但这并不是发生的事情。
And it turns out that even though that
seems reasonable, that's not what happens.
结果是它先把它逼到了一个数字，或者
It turns out that it goes ahead and
coerces it to a number first, or
至少这才是最有可能发生的事情
at least that's what appears to happen.
你注意到我在 7 号线路上没找到 5 号线
You notice that I didn't get back
the string 5 there on line 7,
我恢复了 5 号
I got back the number 5.
所以它确实是在某种意义上
So it does go ahead and
modify, in a sense,
如果需要将其强制转换为数字，那么在执行任何递增操作之前，该值都是必需的。
the value if it needs to coerce it to
a number, before it does any incrementing.
所以它甚至不是真正的一个之后，就在中间。
So it's not even really an after,
it's sort of in the middle.
这件事很奇怪
It's kind of a strange thing.
这是一个从未发生过的细微差别。
And this was a nuance that had
never occurred to me before.
现在我不是建议你用代码来解决这些问题。
Now I'm not suggesting that you're gonna
run across these problems in code.
但这说明了一个更大的点
But this is to be illustrative
of a larger point,
就是我们的开发者倾向于对代码进行心理模型。
which is that we as developers tend
to assume mental models about code.
当虫子发生的时候我说什么时候
And then when bugs happen,
and I say when, not if,
当虫子发生时我们要责怪语言对吧
when bugs happen we blame the language,
right?
我们将此归咎于语言。
We blame the language.
显然， JavaScript 必须设计不佳，因为发生了这种情况。
JavaScript clearly must have been
designed poorly because this happened.
现在我有很多意见。
Now I have lots of opinions.
跟我一样的人知道，我有很多关于 JavaScript的意见。
Those that follow me know,
I have lots of opinions on JavaScript.
我绝不会为那些损失而损失
I'm never at a loss for those.
我想说我唯一的专家就是我自己的意见，对吧 ?
I like to say the only thing I'm
an expert on is my own opinions, right?
我绝不会为那些损失而损失
I'm never at a loss for those.
所以我有很多意见，是不是某方面是好的，
So I have lots of opinions on whether or
not some particular thing was a good or
在设计 JavaScript时做出明智或明智的决策。
smart or
wise decision in the design of JavaScript.
但我从未想过的是
But what I never think
is appropriate is for
我们要去做一件令我们感到惊讶的事情
us to take something where
we get surprised and
说，因为我们很吃惊，所以 JavaScript 是错的。
say, because we're surprised,
therefore JavaScript is at fault.
如果你问一个 C++ 开发者的房间
If you ask a room of C++ developers,
你有没有读过 C++ 规格的任何部分 ?
have you ever read any part
of the specification for C++?
大多数的手会上升，与 Java相同。
Most hands will go up, same for Java.
但如果我问这个问题，我在全世界都问这个问题。
But if I ask that same question, and I do,
all over the world I ask this question
几乎每次，您有多少人阅读了 JavaScript 规范的任何部分 ?
almost every time, how many of you have
read any part of the JavaScript spec?
我几乎没有手过
And I hardly ever get any hands.
我想我在这里的部分原因是
And I think part of what I'm getting
at here is that many developers in
JavaScript 社区似乎认为 JavaScript 具有低屏障
the JavaScript community seem to think
that JavaScript with its low barrier to
输入应该是可以自动理解的，很直观的，
entry, should be so automatically
understandable, so intuitive,
如果它不太直观，那么设计不好。
that if it's not immediately intuitive,
therefore it was poorly designed.
就像我们没有责任去了解我们的工具是如何运作的。
As if we don't own a responsibility
to learn how our tool works.
所以如果你在寻找任何我教书的主题
So if you're looking for any sort of
overarching theme to what I teach and
为什么我要教，尤其是这个课程，那是不够好的
why I teach and specifically this course,
it is that that's not good enough
作为开发商让我们假设一些东西，我们的假设是不正确的。
as developers for us to assume something,
our assumption to be incorrect.
当我们被咬的时候，我们把责任推给别人。
And then when we get bitten by it
we shift the blame to someone else.
而不是其他社区的开发者说
Instead of most developers
in other communities saying,
那是我自己的错
well, the fault is my own.
我还没明白好吗
I didn't understand it enough, okay?
所以在这里，当我遇到它的时候，它是第五号，而不是字符串 5，
So here, when I experienced it coming back
as the number 5 instead of the string 5,
我没说愚蠢的 JavaScript 你怎么能这么设计呢
I didn't say, stupid JavaScript,
how could you be so poorly designed?
我的问题是为什么，具体是什么 ?
My question was why, what specifically?
只有一种方法来回答这个问题。
And there's really only one
way to answer that question.
所以你有没有读过说明书的任何部分
So the question of have you ever
read any part of the specification
是一个一直存在的问题你应该一直在问自己
is really an ever-present question that
you should always be asking yourself.
如果我不明白这一权威的来源在哪里呢 ?
If I don't understand something,
where is that source of authority?
我最近才有这个说法，有人说，我不知道，
I actually had this argument recently
where somebody said, I don't know,
JavaScript 引擎是权限的源。
the JavaScript engine is
the source of authority.
不不可能
No, it isn't.
规范是权限的来源。
The specification is
the source of authority.
如果你想知道为什么会这么做，我为什么会看到这种行为呢 ?
And if you're wondering why does something
do it, why am I seeing this behavior?
为什么它看起来很奇怪或神秘或者黑盒子或狗车什么的
Why does it seem weird or mysterious or
black box or buggy or whatever?
你要问的第一个问题是规格说明应该发生什么 ?
The first question you need to ask is what
does the specification say should happen?
然后问我的行为是否符合规格呢 ?
And then ask does my behavior
that I'm seeing match the spec?
如果他们不匹配那么你就有漏洞了
If they don't match, well,
then you have a bug.
但如果它们真的匹配你就会有不同的虫子
But if they do match, then you
have a different sort of a bug and
大脑内部的缺陷是错误的想法
it's a bug inside of your brain
which is incorrect thinking.